- Hey, Penny.
- Hi. You probably don't wanna go in there.
(Leonard:)Why? What are they doing?
(Penny:)You know, the only way I could explain it
would be in a therapist's office with dolls.
Ooh, boy.
- Dr. Cooper's working.
- Yeah, I can see that.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, Halo night, Koothrappali's.
You coming?
(Sheldon:)Oh, yes, it's Halo night.
Let me just dry my tootsies.
- You're not going to Halo night.
- Yes, I am. It's Wednesday.
(Sheldon:)Wednesday's Halo night.
(Ramona:)Didn't a great man once say,
"Science demands nothing less...
...than the fervent and unconditional
dedication of our entire lives"?
- He did.
- And who was that great man?
(Leonard:)Me.
(Sheldon:)- Sorry, Leonard.
- Seriously? You're not coming?
(Sheldon:)You heard her. How can I argue with me?